<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>github on Professional Blog</title><link>https://alister.github.io/tags/github/</link><description>Recent content in github on Professional Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 20:25:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://alister.github.io/tags/github/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Links to Projects</title><link>https://alister.github.io/blog/2022/03/07/links-to-projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 20:25:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alister.github.io/blog/2022/03/07/links-to-projects/</guid><description>Occasionally, I&amp;rsquo;ll write small largely stand-alone projects. If they are static HTML &amp;amp; Javascript-based, then creating them as Github pages, available as sub-directories on this site (beyond all the existing pages here) can be a quick and easy way to show them.
However, there&amp;rsquo;s not been a good way to link to them, and show them off - so this is just the introduction to the new page in the menu above - and the link to some of my projects.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://alister.github.io/projects/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 20:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alister.github.io/projects/</guid><description>2001: Lets keep it simple I designed these flag options a long time ago, around the year 2001, following some discussion (and a competition) on the main moon society mailing list regarding a flag. Several were produced, but they were all very complicated. This was my idea.
Thoughts for a Luna flag. September 2019 On my second visit to An Evening Of Unnecessary Detail, Geoff Marshall (and Vicki!) were one of the guests on-stage.</description></item><item><title>Contributing to open source can be easy</title><link>https://alister.github.io/blog/2014/07/12/contributing-to-open-source-can-be-easy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2014 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alister.github.io/blog/2014/07/12/contributing-to-open-source-can-be-easy/</guid><description>Although I&amp;rsquo;m busy day to day at my current contract *, that isn&amp;rsquo;t to say that my passions outside the office have come to a complete stop. I&amp;rsquo;m still going to regular meetups (like the PHP London Meetup and Docker London), and I&amp;rsquo;m also planning to go to Symfony Live London 2014. I&amp;rsquo;ve also been reading about, and trying some software, and making the odd fix and new code for myself.</description></item></channel></rss>